It allows for passive and constant mobility of the interperitoneal fluid,
それは、腹腔内液の受動的かつ一定の可動性を可能にします。
intraperitoneal.
腹腔内。
It participates in your gait if you have a peritoneal fixation.
腹膜の固定がある場合、歩行に参加します。
The upper limbs, the lower limbs are also an
上肢、下肢もまた、
expansion of your peritoneal sac.
腹膜嚢の拡張です。
What happens here can be the expression of a development here.
ここで起こることは、ここでの発達の表現である可能性があります。
It is a cellular, tissue, molecular continuity.
それは細胞的、組織的、分子的な連続性です。
and even energetic.
そしてエネルギー的でさえあります。
The peritoneum can fixate.
腹膜は固定されることがあります。
You must consider the peritoneum as an active and current organ,
腹膜を活動的で現在の臓器と見なす必要があります。
meaning it has immune protective capabilities.
つまり、免疫防御能力を持っています。
This leads us to have to consider the peritoneum as an organ.
それは、腹膜を臓器として考慮する必要があることを意味します。
The peritoneum releases tissue hormones, prostaglandins,
腹膜は、分泌と吸収に応じて、組織ホルモンであるプロスタグランジンを放出します。
depending on secretion and absorption.
分泌と吸収に応じて。
This means that it will try to maintain a more or less constant fluid volume,
それは、多かれ少なかれ一定の液体量を維持しようとすることを意味します。
which is quite close.
それはかなり近いです。
of cerebrospinal fluid. At the moment I have the integration of my external coelom
脳脊髄液に。私の外側の体腔の統合があるとき、
into
外部の
an internal coelom, it happens in the same dynamic of development as
内部の体腔は、私の神経管の統合と同じ発達のダイナミクスで起こります。
the integration
統合
of my neural tube. It's as if I integrate the amniotic fluid into my
私の神経管の。羊水を私の神経管に統合するようなものです。
neural tube and
神経管と
I integrate the extra-coelomic fluid into my peritoneal system.
私は腹膜系に卵黄嚢外液を統合します。
This ends on the 28th day,
それは28日目に終わります。
it happens at the same time.
それは同時に行われます。
I have a kind of peritoneal volume that always tries to keep a
私は常に一定を保とうとする腹膜の体積を持っています。
constant
一定
to have a homeostatic hydrostatic volume,
恒常性型の静水圧体積を持つために、
both cerebrally and peritoneally.
脳レベルでも腹膜レベルでも。
There is a transmembrane tension that contains interstitial components
間質成分を含む膜貫通張力があります。
of all neighboring organs,
すべての隣接する臓器の、
which is informed about the digestive state, about the metabolic state
消化状態、代謝状態について情報を受け取ります。
of all surrounding organs.
すべての周囲の臓器の。
in its interstitial fluid.
その間質液中に。
There is no inside.
内部はありません。
It's an exchange together.
それは全体的な交換です。
There are molecular exchanges.
分子交換があります。
I have mesenchymal cells
私は間葉系細胞を持っています。
that were beyond the precordial plate
それは前索板を超えていました。
which will become the pericardium and the septum transversum
それは心膜と横中隔になります。
which are integrated by the global movement of my embryo.
私の胚の全体的な動きによって統合されています。
And at the moment I have this development of the heart
そして、心臓が発達するこの瞬間、
that is setting up, which is a fulcrum,
それは支点となるものであり、
there is a meeting of the heart on the upper part of my vesicle.
私の小胞の上部で心臓が出会います。
And this meeting will integrate these mesenchymal cells that can express themselves
そして、この出会いが、発現しうるこれらの間葉系細胞を統合し、
and form the primitive septum transversum.
原始横中隔を形成します。
And this primitive septum transversum integrates between the 22nd day and closes,
そして、この原始横中隔は22日目から統合され、
we could say, in a delimited way around the 28th day.
28日目頃には限定的に閉鎖すると言えるでしょう。
The peritoneum is an organ in which there are arterioles that have an osmotic exchange
腹膜は、血液プラズマと浸透圧型の交換を行う細動脈を持つ器官です。
with blood plasma.
血液プラズマと。
So there are kinds of exudates that inform it.
したがって、それを知らせる滲出液のようなものがあります。
on the intracellular vegetative state,
細胞内の植物状態について、
that it is all the time and completely,
それは常に完全に、
by this plasma exchange, informed.
この血漿交換によって情報が伝えられています。
There are mesothelial cells like macrophages,
マクロファージのような中皮細胞、
like polymorphonuclear cells, like mast cells,
多核白血球、肥満細胞のような、
which will determine defense reactions at the peritoneal level.
腹膜レベルで防御反応を決定します。
Mast cells are sensitive to immunoglobulins E, to IgE.
肥満細胞は免疫グロブリンE、IgEに敏感です。
So everything that is allergy, asthma, etc.,
したがって、アレルギー、喘息など、すべてが、
are the same mast cells that are present at the level of the article.
気管支のレベルに存在するのと同じ肥満細胞が、感染因子による攻撃があったときに、
bronchial that when you have an aggression of an infectious agent at the level of the
腹膜に感染因子による攻撃があった場合、別のレベルで肥満細胞の脱顆粒を引き起こす可能性があります。
level. I'm allergic to milk, I have a poor immune barrier at the level of
牛乳アレルギーがあり、私の膜の免疫バリアが弱い。通過すべきでない高分子が通過する。
my membrane. Macromolecules that should not pass, pass. There is a
肥満細胞反応が起こる。どうすればいいのか？喘息反応、気管支炎が、
mast cell reaction. What do I do? An asthmatic reaction, bronchitis
外部空間で起こる。感染因子はもともと腹膜にあるのに。
peritoneal.
腹膜にあるのに。
Because I have this same balance in terms of IgE.
なぜなら、私はIgEのレベルで同じバランスを持っているからです。
But I'm going to have a distant reaction.
しかし、私は遠隔反応を起こすでしょう。
I have eczema in a child.
私は子供に湿疹を起こさせます。
Good job, my friend, you found a correct way out.
よくやった、君は正しい出口を見つけた。
We're going to try to remove the allergen.
アレルゲンを取り除こうとします。
But there, you found a way out.
しかし、そこで、あなたは出口を見つけました。
We're going to give you cortisone.
コルチゾンを投与します。
I'm bringing it in.
私は中に入れます。
The skin is also an expression of your cerebrospinal fluid,
皮膚はまた、あなたの脳脊髄液の表現でもあります。
in its earliest expression on the autogenetic level.
自己発生的な観点から最も初期の表現において。
But it is also an expression of your tube.
しかし、それはまた、あなたの管の表現でもあります。
digestive. The digestive tract is an external tissue. And so, what I'm trying to make
消化器。消化管は外部の組織です。したがって、私がここで出そうとしているものを、
come out here, if it's blocked, I'll express it here.
もしそれがブロックされたら、私はここでそれを表現するでしょう。
And at the level of the digestive tract, how
消化管のレベルでは、どのように
do I express it? I express it either by asthma, because I will
表現するのでしょうか？喘息として表現するかもしれません。なぜなら、私はそれを
demacify it, or by
取り除くか、あるいは
bronchitis. I'm going to produce mucus, an exudate. I'm going to get it
気管支炎として表現するからです。粘液、滲出液の産生を排出します。私はそれを
out as
できる限り
best I can. I'm going to give you bronchodilators now.
排出します。今、気管支拡張剤を投与します。
I'm going to give antibiotics but I haven't solved the problem, it was perhaps simply
抗生物質を投与しますが、問題は解決していません。それは単に
an allergen like a strawberry
イチゴのようなアレルゲンだったのかもしれません。